<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-06-25T01:24:55.722Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The Vegan Stoner Cookbook]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6281</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/the-vegan-stoner-cookbook"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis consumers and those who adopt a vegan lifestyle have much more in common than you may realize. For one, deciding to remedy illnesses naturally and holistically is a considerable factor in why humans use weed, and it’s also a fundamental reason for choosing raw, natural ingredients to eat. Many surveys suggest that people who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Travel Destinations for Stoners]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6305</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/best-stoner-vacations"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If traveling is one of your favorite hobbies, it doesn’t have to exclude weed; you just have to know where to go. There are weed-friendly places to visit worldwide and even popular cannabis tourism here in the United States. From flying with weed to cannabis-friendly resorts, lounges, and events, cannabis culture as we know it [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spraying Terpenes on Weed]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6663</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/spraying-terpenes-on-weed"/>
        <updated>2022-06-20T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terpenes are what provide the sweet aroma and flavor of your favorite buds. They can also enhance the potency and physical characteristics of cannabis plants. Lately, terpenes spray has been a big hit among cannabis consumers, but why? Join us as we break down the basics of terpenes and the recreational and medical benefits of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Weed Mold Look Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5138</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/weed-mold"/>
        <updated>2022-06-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since medical and recreational marijuana legalization has gained momentum, there has been more cannabis plant recalls in the past few years in states like Colorado, California, Michigan, and Florida due to health hazards from smoking moldy marijuana. Cannabis plants can begin to grow mold in the growing, drying, or curing stages. It becomes more susceptible [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Strain for Beginner Growers]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4855</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/best-strain-for-beginner-growers"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can homegrown weed be good? Homegrown weed can absolutely be good! High-quality homegrown marijuana can be better for your health than most cannabis products you’ll get from a dispensary. Home growing is likely your best bet if you enjoy knowing exactly what goes into your cannabis plants during the cultivation process. What is a strain? [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete Guide To Delta 10 THC]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5111</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/complete-guide-to-delta-10-thc"/>
        <updated>2022-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Basics of Delta THC Several variations of THC, called chemical analogs, work to distinguish various types of THC from one another. These unique THC compounds are all slightly different. These differences impact how the human body’s endocannabinoid system reacts to them. Some analogs are federally illegal, while another active ingredient may be allowed. 3 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CBD Addictive?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5147</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cbd/is-cbd-addictive"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBD has grown in popularity since the Farm Bill and federal legalization in 2018, especially within the world of health and wellness. There are many questions asked about the potential risks and benefits of CBD for public health-related problems, and ongoing misconceptions regarding whether it’s safe to use daily or possibly even addictive. Understanding any [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Cannabis Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6259</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/cannabis-coffee"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know if cannabis and coffee go together or if they are better consumed separately, look no further. Today, we are going to help you decide. Visit a dispensary, and you’ll find a vast selection of weed-infused coffees. If you’re anything like us, starting your morning with a cup of coffee is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is THC Syrup?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5597</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/what-is-thc-syrup"/>
        <updated>2022-06-06T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like the thought of trying THC concentrates to improve health conditions but don’t want to smoke weed, or if you want to try new products on the market, THC syrups may be your new favorite way to use cannabis. Cannabis Syrup 101 THC syrup is a cannabis syrup made by mixing cannabis concentrates [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Smoke Weed on Birth Control?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5132</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/health/can-you-smoke-weed-on-birth-control"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since marijuana is still illegal under federal law, scientific research is very limited. Because of the way cannabis interacts with the human body’s endocannabinoid system, certain studies suggest that CBD may be beneficial for those who take birth control, while THC may present an increased risk for others. Further research will surely lead us to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Father’s Day Gift Guide for Cannabis Products]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6041</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/fathers-day-cannabis"/>
        <updated>2022-06-01T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of Father’s Day, Leafy Mate has compiled a list of cannabis-themed gifts for dear dad. Today we take a look into the history of Father’s Day and provide some eccentric gift ideas for a stoner dad that you love. Hopefully, by understanding the origins of the holiday, we can better honor and celebrate [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Colorado Hikes For Cannabis Users]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5912</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/colorado-hikes-for-cannabis-users"/>
        <updated>2022-05-30T14:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis used to enhance your hiking experience is an excellent way to get the most out of being outdoors. Colorado is full of areas to escape into nature to feel its therapeutic benefits, including the infamous Rocky Mountain National park which is home to over two hundred of the best backpacking trails in Colorado. Colorado’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Rick Simpson Oil?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5602</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/what-is-rick-simpson-oil"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created in a Canadian hospital, Rick Simpson Oil (RSO) is a cannabis oil known for its medical benefits, including relieving some cancer symptoms. It has a dark brown color and a thick consistency. You can apply it as a topical or consume it in an edible. Continue reading as we describe who Rick Simpson is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>