<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-27T01:43:54.645Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cannabis Administration and Opportunity Act of 2022- What Will it Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=10860</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/industry/cannabis-administration-and-opportunity-act"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T19:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senate leaders introduced legislation Thursday to remove federal prohibitions on marijuana a half of a century after Congress deemed it illegal. Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer has proposed the Cannabis Administration and Opportunity Act that would federally decriminalize weed and allow states to form their marijuana laws without retribution from Washington D.C. Cannabis Administration and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best THC Detox Methods in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5108</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/best-thc-detox-methods"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A thorough collection of THC detox methods and brands to help you pass a drug test quickly and effectively. Need to Pass a Drug Test? Recently, cannabis use has been legalized in many states on a medical or recreational level, but you still may encounter careers or organizations that require mandatory drug tests. If you’ve [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Popular Fertilizers for Growing Cannabis]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5087</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/best-fertilizers-for-marijuanas"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your go-to guide on locating, purchasing, and using the top organic fertilizers for cannabis plants in 2022. Cannabis Plant Cycle Cannabis has four main stages of plant growth. It’s important to understand which cannabis nutrients and how much to provide during each step. Step 1: Germination The seed germination life stage can last anywhere from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best 24 Hour Dispensary Near Me]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5590</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/best-24-hour-dispensary-near-me"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the legal cannabis industry is booming, cultivation and dispensary jobs are increasing. In 2020, the marijuana industry employed a quarter of a million people, and sales exceeded twenty billion dollars. As more states legalize weed and begin to farm and sell it, the legal sector will create more jobs. Cannabis Legal Status Since recreational [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Cannabis Leaves Can Tell You]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4861</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/what-cannabis-leaves-can-tell-you"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re a novice grower or are well on your way to mastering grower level, it’s crucial to know the differences in cannabis leaves and how to understand the signs of healthy and unhealthy plant growth. Here, we provide you with the tools to fully utilize the leaves of your cannabis plant for a bigger [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Grow Room]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4846</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/what-is-a-grow-room"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A grow room or grow tent is a designated space of a specific size where plants are grown in a controlled environment. Some people use a grow room to avoid the legal repercussions of home growing weed, while others have little to no outdoor space available. Is it safe to grow weed at home? It [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invest In Cannabis Stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4867</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/industry/invest-in-cannabis-stocks"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T14:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with any new industry, there are many potential investment risks with buying cannabis stocks. Whether you’re a first-time or experienced investor, understanding how this industry works will pay off. Our guide will provide you with the basics and includes our top choices for the marijuana stocks to invest in this year. Cannabis Industry Climate [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabinoids 101: What Makes Cannabis Medicine?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5593</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/what-makes-cannabis-medicine"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T15:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabinoids are the chemicals inside cannabis and marijuana plants. In a nutshell, they are the chemical compounds in marijuana that cause people to feel high and the active ingredients in cannabis that produce certain therapeutic effects. While many people think of two cannabinoids like tetrahydrocannabinol (THC), the chemical in marijuana that produces psychoactive effects, or [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 Medical Marijuana Dispensaries in Mesa, AZ]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5931</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/best-dispensaries-in-mesa-az"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis has been legal for recreational adult use in Arizona since 2020, and medical marijuana has been legal since 2010 for qualified patients and caregivers. The result has been a thriving cannabis industry that continues to push the limits of legal weed markets, cultivation, and overall industry culture. As legalization becomes more predominant in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is 710 Day?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=6308</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/what-is-710-day"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within cannabis culture, 710 Day is basically International Dab Day according to Urban Dictionary. 710 is considered a holiday celebrated on July 10th for many cannabis consumers that enjoy cannabis oil products like dabs or concentrates. The term 710 rotated and upside down spells OIL, a word used to describe these highly potent cannabis products. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Aquaponics?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5135</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/what-is-aquaponics"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide for first-time aquaponics growers, filled with tools and tips you’ll need to grow cannabis plants with water at home. Cannabis Cultivation According to a 2017 chart by Marijuana Business Daily, the average cost of weed cultivation per square foot is $45.00. To break that number down further: An indoor grower will spend up [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>