<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-03T01:24:28.910Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://leafymate.github.io/cannabis-resources/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis Oil For Brain Cancer Treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5090</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/health/cannabis-oil-for-brain-cancer-treatment"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T12:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is brain cancer? A brain tumor is basically a mass of abnormal cancer cells growing within your brain.Many different types of brain tumors exist. Some brain tumors are noncancerous, and some brain tumors are cancerous. Brain tumors can begin in your brain, start in other parts of your body as lung cancer, bladder cancer, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis Breeding 101]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5084</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/growing/cannabis-breeding-101"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis breeding and cultivation is an art that can only be perfected by knowing the ins and outs of the cannabis plant. If you’re interested in getting started with growing or creating a new cannabis strain, continue reading for more information. Cannabis plant anatomy You’ll need to know the specific parts of the male and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Got The Best Munchies: East Coast vs West Coast]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5231</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/whos-got-the-best-munchies"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the Munchies? Urban Dictionary describes the munchies as “the compelling and intense feeling of hunger after smoking weed.” While accurate, there is an even more scientific explanation for this feeling. Read on to find out more about what causes a munchies hit and the best snack to relieve those intense cravings. What causes [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis Friendly Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5144</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/industry/cannabis-friendly-banks"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Options for cannabis banking are still minimal for marijuana entrepreneurs, even though thirty-seven states have legalized medical marijuana and seventeen states permit recreational adult use. Since the federal government still categorizes marijuana as an illegal Schedule 1 drug, national banks fear that doing business with a cannabis-related business means they could violate federal law. Due [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemp Dog Treats]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5240</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/hemp-dog-treats"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For pet owners, there are endless supplements out there for your pet, but one that’s been popular lately is hemp oil. You may have heard of it for human wellness and anxiety relief, but its organic ingredients can also be helpful for dogs. From its potential physical health benefits to dosage information, let’s go over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemp Oil For Headaches]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4864</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/health/hemp-oil-for-headaches"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis use for migraine relief has become a noticeable health trend in recent years, but many cultures have used the plant’s pain-relieving effects for thousands of years. The legalization of cannabis in over half of the U.S. states has prompted scientists to ramp up the research and testing processes. Many research organizations are diving into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Jobs are in The Cannabis Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5099</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/industry/what-jobs-are-in-the-cannabis-industry"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are interested in a cannabis career, continue reading as we go over the top marijuana jobs and some of the recently trending cannabis businesses. Your Cannabis Career With the legalization of recreational marijuana in many American states, more jobs are in demand within the legal cannabis sector than ever before. A recent report [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[420 Celebrations]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5234</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/420-celebrations"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[420 is celebrated worldwide. The largest celebration in the world occurs yearly in Denver, Colorado for the Mile High 420 Festival. However, now there are events with multiple vendors all over the U.S. in cities like Washington D.C., Las Vegas, Portland, and San Francisco. Internationally there are also many places that host parties on April [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recipe: CBD Queso And Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5243</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cbd/cbd-queso-and-chips"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April 20 steadily approaching, what better way to celebrate than creating your own CBD queso recipe to treat yourself and your close friends. Read on as we share all the tips for ensuring you have the best munchies at the party. How Weed Edibles Work Edibles are a discreet and exciting way to try [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is 420?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5228</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/what-is-420"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people know that 4:20 is an international holiday to celebrate and partake in cannabis consumption. However, not many people, even marijuana users, know the real origin behind connecting the number 420 to the cannabis plant itself. A few older stories describe how this national holiday and 4:20 as a special time of day became [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classic Strains From The 60s That Are Still Available Today]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5120</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/classic-strains-from-the-60s-that-are-still-available-today"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many classic marijuana strains that have been around for centuries. Some of the classic strains have become parent strains to the top marijuana plants in the world today. Read on as we discuss the evolution of marijuana and how that led to the cultivation of the most famous strains of our time. This [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovative Women In The Cannabis Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5102</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/industry/innovative-women-in-the-cannabis-industry"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The demand for female representation in the workplace has significantly increased over the past decade; however, many industries continue to struggle to create gender equality within their companies, especially at the executive levels. The cannabis industry, however, has incorporated female influence and leadership since its’ start. The cannabis industry has been a haven for a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History of Workplace Drug Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5123</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/history-of-workplace-drug-testing"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workplace drug screening is a controversial topic in American politics. Some feel that it is an outdated practice that began at the height of the War On Drugs. Others think it’s necessary to establish a workplace drug testing program for morality and safety reasons. But, where do companies draw the line? What drugs are tested [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Holy Men In India Use Weed For Spiritual Purposes]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5117</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/weed-for-spiritual-purposes"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis use is involved in spiritual rituals all over the world, weed itself is even celebrated and regarded highly as sacred plants in certain cultures. Join us as we dive into the connection between cannabis and spirituality and the rich history that goes along with it. The History of Cannabis and Spirituality Many religions and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find The Perfect Strain To Match Your Lifestyle]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=5114</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/lifestyle/find-the-perfect-strain-to-match-your-lifestyle"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T02:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Strain is Perfect for Me? This is a question many newcomers to consuming cannabis may be asking. It can be an intense process considering there are hundreds of different types of marijuana strains in the world today. Read on and allow us to guide you in the right direction towards your ideal weed strain. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Cannabis Dependence?]]></title>
        <id>https://leafymate.com/resources/?p=4849</id>
        <link href="https://leafymate.com/resources/cannabis-101/cannabis-dependence"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T15:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Leafy Mate, we try to lighten the mood whenever we can. The below clip is a timeless track by rapper Afroman, who released it in the year 2001 during a decade when stoner comedies dominated the box office. Based on the way marijuana use impacts his daily life and activities, Afroman strongly suggests he [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leafy Mate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>